Let us mention the big stocks which are
very important from the market point of view.
Sir, first of all we were talking about the importance of ICICI Bank 1445 level.
Where did you reach today?  The line
came down Sir ICICI Bank.  Yes, it will not cross 1445.
He goes to 1445 three times a week and comes
back after eating his food.   The
level of 1400 was touched below.  Still, there has been a
very good recovery from there.  I felt a little relieved
that I had recovered a little from there.
today's this is only 1420 made so far
more.  Yes.  No, I will not buy it until it closes above 1445.
My funda is very
clear. To show its strength, it
needs to close above 1445.  Secondly,
I know you will ask about HDFC Bank
[laughs]
so Neha ji, in HDFC Bank, there is a
dilemma between short term and long term.   If
you look at the short term, HDFC Bank
is weak and I had told you with the data that in
January 2024 and January 2025, it happened twice
when the RSC RSI of HDFC Bank remained below 25
and from there the stock made gains in January 2024
after falling a little more,
made gains of 15% in 3 months and in 2025
made gains of 21% in 3 months, so HDFC Bank gives such a big
jump when the RSI is oversold, it
is trying even today, ah, it
reached the lowest level of almost 9 months, where did HDFC Bank go?
91950 920 The low of yesterday and the day before yesterday was also 920.
So HDFC Bank is currently trading at its lowest level in 9 months.
If it
stays above 940 for two-three days, then
either buy it there or do
weekly SIP in it for the next four weeks or six weeks
or if it falls by 1% then do SIP of 5% on fall, 5% on fall and
6% on fall and 1% on fall and 1% on fall.
If you are an investor, then
now is the opportunity for SIP investors to buy in HDFC Bank.
Last year
too, we had recommended this stock during Diwali.
From there, good money was made at 17, 18%, 15%.
15% in HDFC Bank is
not less by any means.   This would be
considered a very good return.  If a
stock like HDFC Bank gives such returns,
doubles your FD, then it will be considered good.
Now again HDFC Bank can slowly
give you the opportunity to invest.
All right.  So, among the two big banks,
this opinion is being made for you right now among the two big stocks of Nifty, ICICI Bank and
HDFC Bank.